maastars.com 2011-12-31

# maastars.com privacy policy movie artists association website maastars | MaaStars

**maastars.com** intends all its users to feel comfortable using our web sites and secured while submitting information to us.  The users are free to contact us with your questions or concerns about privacy on this site.  We let the users know that by using our sites you are giving us your free consent to the collection of certain data.

The following Privacy Statement discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for maastars.com website.

Our Site, like most other sites, uses cookies to provide you with a more personalized and user-friendly experience. A cookie is a message that is sent to a browser from a Web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies help us keep track of the size of our audience, the frequency of visits to our Site and the areas that are most popular. We may also use cookies to help us deliver content or advertising specific to your interests, and to save your preferences or passwords so you don’t have to re-enter them each time you visit our Site. Most browsers allow you to reject all cookies, but then your preferences, passwords and other information will not be saved, and you may have to re-enter information to use certain features of our Site.

We may use an outside ad company to display ads on our Site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, our ad company collects cookies delivered through banner ads, and we do not have access to this information.  Maastars.com may also serve banner ads that contain cookies. We will only share such information with our advertisers and sponsors on an aggregate basis to determine the success of any given banner, logo or advertisement.

In general, we will not disclose your personal information to third parties except to the extent necessary to provide you with a requested service, or under circumstances required by law. We will disclose your personal information when we believe in good faith that any applicable law, regulation, or legal process requires it, or where we believe disclosure is necessary to protect or enforce our rights or the rights of another user. We also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our services and reach to prospective partners, advertisers, and other third parties. However, aggregate data is not traceable to you specifically. We may use contractors to help us with our operations. Some or all of these contractors may access our databases of user information. These contractors will enter into an agreement with us that place restrictive provisions on their use and disclosure of all information they obtain through the relationship.

1\. We will collect anonymous traffic information from you when you visit our site.

2\. We will collect personally identifiable information about you only as part of a voluntary registration process, on-line survey or contest.

3\. Our advertisers may collect anonymous traffic information from their own assigned cookies to your browser.

4\. The Site contains links to other Web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such Web sites.

5\. Any personal information or content that is voluntarily disclosed online by the users becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others. We have no control over its use and you should exercise caution when disclosing your personal information to anyone.

We use personal information to:

1\. Help us provide personalized features

2\. Tailor our sites to your interest

3\. Get in touch with you when necessary

We use contact information internally to:

1\. Direct our efforts for product improvement

2\. Contact you as a survey respondent

3\. Notify you if you win any contest

4\. Send you promotional materials from our contest sponsors or advertisers

Generally, we use anonymous traffic information to:

1\. Remind us of whom you are in order to deliver to you a better and more personalized service from both advertising and an editorial perspective

2\. Recognize your access privileges to our Web sites

3\. Track your entries in some of our promotions, sweepstakes and contests to indicate a player’s progress through the promotion and to track entries, submissions, and status in prize drawings

4\. Make sure that you don’t see the same ad repeatedly

5\. Help diagnose problems with our server

6\. Administer our Web sites

7\. Track your session so that we can understand better how people use our sites

We will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information to third parties unless:

1\. We have your permission

2\. Special circumstances such as compliance with legal authorities require disclosure

All sites that are customizable require that you accept cookies. You also must accept cookies to register as someone for access to some of our services. For information on how to set your browser to alert you to cookies, or to reject cookies, go to http://www.cookiecentral.com/faq/.

To protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control, we have in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures. For example, our servers are accessible only to authorized personnel.

Although we will endeavor to safeguard the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information, transmissions made by means of the Internet cannot be made absolutely secure. By using this site, you agree that we will have no liability for disclosure of your information due to errors in transmission or unauthorized acts of third parties.

We use a few third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

To correct or update any information you have provided, our site gives you the following option for changing:

Send an e-mail to maastars.com

We reserve the right to change or update these policies at any time upon reasonable notice, effective immediately upon posting to this site.

**maastars.com**
